androidcommunity.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Android Community

The following policy outlines the types of information that we gather about you and the way that way we use and don’t use this information.

The information that we collect about our visitors falls into three general categories:

1\. Information You Provide to Us. We may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply to us either on the AndroidCommunity site, via e-mail, or in any other way. Some examples of this type of information include the information you submit (such as your name or e-mail address) when you register for AndroidCommunity membership, information that you post on blog entry comment, and information contained in search requests or questions you submit to the site. If you decline to supply or provide us with certain information, we may not be able to provide you with some services that are dependent on the collection of this information.

2\. Information that is Automatically Collected. We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate through the AndroidCommunity site. For example, to enhance your experience at AndroidCommunity, we use a standard feature found in browser software called a “cookie.” Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use our site, cookies help us track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of our site where you have entered preference information before. Another example of information that we automatically collect as you navigate our site is information about your computer’s connection to the Internet. This information allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on our site.

3\. Information from Other Sources. AndroidCommunity may also obtain information about you from third parties or other sources and may combine the information that we receive from them with information we have already obtained about you.

AndroidCommunity includes links to other websites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase products or services or conduct other transactions through the Service, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

4\. Third Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this Web Site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses’ privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative‘s consumer web site.

Questions on Privacy

If you have questions or concerns about the children’s privacy statement, the privacy practices of the AndroidCommunity site, or your dealings with AndroidCommunity, please contact us.
